Guide to the Margaret S. Mahler Psychiatric Research Foundation Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1982, undated; Accession 1998-M-083
  - "Basic" Film-Reel 1-Symbiosis and Differentiation, undated (Box 2)
  - "Basic" Film-Reel 2-Practicing Subphase, undated (Box 2)
  - "Basic" Film-Reel 3-Rapprochement, undated (Box 3)
  - Infant-Reel 1 of 2, undated (Box 4–5)
  - Infant-Reel 1 of 2, undated (Box 6)
  - Infant-Reel 2 of 2, undated (Box 6)
  - The Self-A Wind Opt Track, undated (Box 7)
  - The Self-A and B Rolls, undated (Box 7)
  - The Self-Part I (2 films), undated (Box 8)
  - The Self-Part II (2 films), undated (Box 9)
  - "On Some Phenomena Indicative of the Emergence of the Self," 1982 (Box 10)